{
    "subject": "resource/Croatian_Radiotelevision",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Hrvatska radiotelevizija",
    "human_readable": "The name of Croatian Radiotelevision is Hrvatska radiotelevizija.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9313425421714783,
            "question": "What is the name of Croatian Radiotelevision?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8917891979217529,
            "question": "Does Hrvatska radiotelevizija operate television channels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8646867275238037,
            "question": "Where is Hrvatska radiotelevizija based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8455916047096252,
            "question": "Is Hrvatska radiotelevizija a broadcasting organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7676812410354614,
            "question": "What are some popular programs aired by Hrvatska radiotelevizija?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7438236474990845,
            "question": "Does Hrvatska radiotelevizija offer radio programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7158549427986145,
            "question": "What services does Hrvatska radiotelevizija provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7125107049942017,
            "question": "When was Hrvatska radiotelevizija founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7039835453033447,
            "question": "Is Hrvatska radiotelevizija a public or private organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6934335231781006,
            "question": "What language is primarily used by Hrvatska radiotelevizija?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Croatian Radiotelevision is Hrvatska radiotelevizija.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5013_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hrvatska radiotelevizija a public or private organization?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5013_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Hrvatska radiotelevizija founded?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5013_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What services does Hrvatska radiotelevizija provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5013_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5013_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I can answer your question as follows:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, it is indeed stated that the name of Croatian Radiotelevision is Hrvatska radiotelevizija. This is mentioned in several files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5013/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5013/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt, etc.) and the information is consistent across all files."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided documents mention that the official name for Croatian Radiotelevision in Croatian is \"Hrvatska radiotelevizija,\" which supports the statement that the name of Croatian Radiotelevision is Hrvatska radiotelevizija."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}